Guide to the Medical Center Public Relations records, 1913-1999 RG0045
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Medical Center Public Relations records
1913-1999
1960-1991
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Medical Center. Office of Communications and Marketing
RG0045
49 Linear Feet
Collection includes biographical files, photographs, slides, videotapes, press kits, publications, books, and artifacts.
Restrictions on Access
Series 7 is closed to research for 75 years from date of record creation.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from the Director of Medical Center Public Relations.
Historical Note
Medical Center Public Relations at The George Washington University became the Medical Center Office of Communications and Marketing, circa 1999. It was previously known as the Department of Marketing and Public Relations (c.1994-99) and before that the Office of Public Relations. It publishes "Progress" (1989-Present), which evolved from the "Friday Report" (1970-89), and "GW Health and Medicine magazine" (1965-Present). The Director of Medical Center Public Relations reports to the Director of the Medical Center. The office also maintains publicity files on staff and faculty.
N.B. This history note was written in 2005.
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include biographical files, photographs, slides, videotapes, press kits, publications, books, and artifacts. They range in date from 1960-91, and were transferred to the University Archives by the Director of Medical Center Public Relations. Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into fourteen series: five relate to faculty and five are visual materials. The remaining four are as listed: Medical Center history, Articles, Graduating class, and Departmental files.
Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Photographs; Publications; Washington (D.C.); Faculty; Black-and-white slides; Biography; Color slides; Employees; Events; Blades, Brian; Aaron, Benjamin L.; Sizoo, Joseph Richard; Watts, James W. (James Winston); George Washington University. Ross Hall; Bloedorn, W. A. (Walter Andrew); Brady, Luther W.; George Washington University. Medical Center; George Washington University; Miller, Frank Nelson; Reagan, Ronald; Roe,, Joseph
- Faculty biographical files, ca.1950-1989; RG0045 Series 1; 3 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series has documents that provide biographical information of Medical Center faculty including teaching information, specialist area information, reports, photographs, clippings, general correspondence, and miscellaneous papers. They range in date from ca.1950-1989.
  - Abramson, Herbert, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, John P., undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adkins, Paul, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alford, T.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Angel, J. Lawrence, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Atkins, David L., undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Benedict, Ruth B., undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Black, Emilie A., undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Brandt, Linda, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Breen, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Clark, Rolf, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Danish, Abraham W., undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - DeMoya, Armando, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Duggins, Virginia A., undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Enos, William F., undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Epstein, Julius R., undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Fiacco, Anthony V., undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Fox, Ray R., undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Frederickson, Donald S., undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - George, Lynn, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Green, David C., undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Hufford, Terry L., undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Jamieson, Sally B., undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Jarman, Burnice H., undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Kaufman, Ronald P., undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Kogan, Leo, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Krulfeld, Ruth M., undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Levine, Jack L., undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Lewis, J.H., undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Lyles, Johnnie, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Margileth, Andrew, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Marlow, William H., undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Marsh, William L., undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Martin, Charles, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Parker, James S., undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Pearson, Jed, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Price, Neel J., undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Rhame, Richard C., undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Ryan, Mike, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Stolar, Myer H., undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Sugar, Samuel J.N., undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Townsend, Charles E., undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - VanHouten, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Walls, Ron, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Walsh, James C., undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Withers, Maida, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Albert, Solomon, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Beachley, Ralph G., undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bloedorn, Walter A., undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Borden, Daniel L., undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Borden, William C., undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Brainin, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Breslow, Alexander, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Caceres, C.A., undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Carlson, Paul, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chalfant, W. Paxson, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chiu, Wu S., undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - DeBoard, Patricia A., undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Epstein, Jerome, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Ferguson, Edward E., undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Frederickson, Donald S., undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Freeman, Walter, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Frieman, Joseph M., undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Geier, Fred A.J., undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Griffin, Angus M., undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Halberstam, Michael J., undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Hellebower, Roy C., undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Holly, Pearl, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Horowitz, Alex, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Hyde, Dean L., undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Kelser, George A., undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Kilstein, Richard I., undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Meyer, Eugene & Agnes, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Morris, E.K., undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Mourad, Mahmoud, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Murty, Challakonda, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Nathanson, Esther, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Nelson, Warren J., undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Newman, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - O'Reilly, Sean, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Paine, Richmond S., undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Parr, Leland W., undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Platt, Mark, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Rice, Clarence E., undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Robert, Evie, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Roe, Joseph H., undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Roth, George B., undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Seifter, Joseph, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Sizoo, Joseph R., undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Stanbro, William W., undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Stolar, Myer H., undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Ticktin, Howard, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Vahouny, George V., undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Valaske, Martin, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Vinson, Fred, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Watt, Mary, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - White, Charles S., undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Wise, Charles, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Wright, Willard, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Wyman, Alvin, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Faculty biographical files, RG0045 Series 2; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains files with biographical data for retired and/or deceased faculty members.
  - Andersen, Elizabeth Potts, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bailey, Dr. William Otis Jr., undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barr, Soloman Efram, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bever, Christopher T. Jr., undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cunningham, Edward E., undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Margaret, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - DePalma, Ralph, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Donnely, Orville Wright, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ehrlich, Bernard H., undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Erkenback, Richard Vernon, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Fuchs, Dr. Martin, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Gahres, Edward E., undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Glew, William B., undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Gold, Harvey R., undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Harris, Forest Klaire II, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Harrison, Dr. Isabella, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Hartman, Dr. Thomas L., undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Horowitz, Dr. Norman, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Kaufman, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Keshishian, Dr. John Mark, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Lehrman, Dr. Harold B., undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Marlow, John L., undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Mazel, Dr. Paul, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Meyers, Frederick, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Miller, George F., undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Milowe, Dr. Irvin D., undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Movassaghi, Dr. Nasser, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Myrianthopoulos, Ntinos C., undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Peele, Dr. Roger, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Perry, Dr. Lowell, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Reiss, David, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Robinowitz, Dr. Carolyn B., undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Robinson, Dr. Luther, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Robinson, Dr. Mary, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Romansky, Dr. Monroe J., undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Rose, Dr. Morton H., undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Ross, Dr. Sydney, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Rovner, Irwin, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Spurlock, Dr. Jeanne, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Stark, Dr. William, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Faculty biographical files, RG0045 Series 3; 4.5 Linear feet
  This series contains biographical files and photographs of faculty members.
  - Dr. Albert, Chalom, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dr. Al-Doory, Yousef, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    General note
    (photo in box 3)
  - Dr. Alford, Crandall, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Alpert, Seymour, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Scope and Contents
    Please note this file is currently missing.
  - Dr. Alstatt, Alice, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dr. Bennet, Linda, Ph.D., undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Blades, Brian, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Bourne, Peter, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dr. Brailler, David, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dr. Brennan, Gloria, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dr. Brody, David, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Brown, Halla, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Brudno, Spencer, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Dr. Butler, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Chen, Harry, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Cioffi, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Dr. Coakley, Charles, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Cole, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Dr. Corn, Milton, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dr. Constantinople, Nicholas, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dr. Cooper, Theodore, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dr. Craft, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Dr. D'Agostino, Angelo, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dr. Dennis, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Dr. Devita, Vincent, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Dr. DiGioia, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Dr. Dodek, Samuel, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Dr. Doyle, Brian, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Dr. Drum, Bruce, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Dr. Duncan, Harry, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Dr. Dupont, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Dr. Eckelman, William, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Dr. Ecker, Henry, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Dr. Evans, Mark, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Dr. Elliott, Lloyd, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Dr. Feffer, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Dr. Feffer, Henry Leon, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Dr. Fabro, Sergio, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Dr. Feinstein, Carl, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Dr. Finnerty, Fran, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Dr. Fones, Diane, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Dr. Footer Marvin, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Dr. Fox, Samuel, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Dr. Freer, Carol, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Dr. Fry, A. Gordon, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Dr. Gaffney, Brian, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Dr. Galioto, Frank, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Dr. Garbedian-Ruffalo, Susan, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Dr. Gaskin, Joe, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Dr. Glew, Donald, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Dr. Goldsmityh, Barbara, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Dr. Gonzalez, Sandra, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Dr. Hendron, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Dr. Hehrer, Gilbert, Ph.D., undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Dr. Hertz, Roy, undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Dr. Hogness, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Dr. Holland, Peter, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Dr. Hufnagel, Charles, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Dr. Hunt, Thelma, undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Iosefsohn, Mariet, undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Dr. Iovine, Vincent, undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Dr. Jacobs, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Dr. Jacobson, Cecil, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Dr. Johnson, William, undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Dr. Katz, Sol, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Dr. Katzen, Barry, undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Dr. Kaufman, Paul, undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Dr. Kavanaugh, Frank, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
    (file missing)
  - Kayser, Elmer, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Dr. Kramer, Norman, undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Dr. Koulouris, Spiros, undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Krueger, Dean, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Dr. Klopp, Calvin, undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Dr. Klug, Panpit, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Dr. Koch, Patricia, undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Dr. Keisling, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Dr. Ling, C. Clifton, undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Dr. Lieberman, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Dr. Lieberman, Roger, undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Dr. Lewis, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Dr. Lewicki, Ann, undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Dr. Levine, Larry, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Dr. Levy, Marie Louise, undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Dr. Letterman, Gordon, undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Dr. Leonard, Fred, undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Dr. Levine, Sidney, undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Dr. Loube, Samuel, undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Dr. Lourie, Reginald, undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Dr. Ludewig, Victor, undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Dr. Lukash, William, undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Dr. McKay, Douglas, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Dr. McKelway, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dr. McMillan, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dr. McSweeney, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dr. Maier, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dr. Makhega, Amar, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Margileth, Andrew, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Marsh, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dr. Meek, Donald, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Dr. Miller, Frank, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Dr. Miller, James, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Naughton, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dr. O' Connor, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Dr. O'Reilly, Sean, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Pierpont, Howard, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Pipberger, Hubert, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dr. Portnoi, Valery, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dr. Radcliffe, Harold, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Dr. Rawls, Ronald, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Dr. Remey, James, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Dr. Rheingold, Jack, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Dr. Romansky, Monroe, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    (photo in box 5)
  - Dr. Rosenbaum, Meyer, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Dr. Roubin, Gary, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Dr. Ruffalo, Richard, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Dr. Sank, Lawrence, Ph.D., undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Dr. Saunders, Robert, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Dr. Savitz, Alan, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Dr. Schechter, Geraldine, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Dr. Schreiner, George, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Dr. Schulman, Cyril, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Dr. Schulman, Joseph, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Dr. Schurter, Maxine, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Dr. Scott, Lewis, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Dr. Shaffer, Carolyn, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Dr. Shapiro, Robert, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Dr. Shapiro, Stephen, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Dr. Shelburne, Samuel, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Sherwood, Karen, R.D., undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Dr. Shumway, Norman, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Dr. Silber, Thomas, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Dr. Silver, Harold, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Silverman, Mary, R.N., undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Dr. Slaby, Andrew, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Dr. Smith, Benjamin, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Dr. Smythe, Nicholas, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Dr. Soloman, Iris, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Dr. Soyster, Peter, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Dr. Speck, George, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Stein, Walter, MHSA, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Dr. Stevens, Harold, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Dr. Stiller, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Dr. Sullivan, Thomas, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Dr. Tauber, Laszlo, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Dr. Taylor, George, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Dr. Thompson, Lewis, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Dr. Thurman, Gary, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Dr. Travell, Janet, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Dr. Treadwell, Carleton, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Dr. Treichler, Howard, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Dr. Trible, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Dr. Tsakonas, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Dr. Turbiak, Thomas, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Dr. Turcios, Nelson, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Dr. Valentino, Rita, Ph.D., undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Dr. Van Handel, Peter, Ph.D., undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Vita, Frank, undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Dr. Wagner, Gerald, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Dr. Wagner, Teekie, undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Dr. Waldhorn, Richard, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Dr. Wamboldt, Frederick, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Waters, Bud, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Dr. Webster, Thomas, undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Dr. Weinstein, Jacob, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Dr. Weisberg, Paul, undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Dr. Wiesel, Sam, undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Dr. Wise, Charles, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Woodward, Jim, undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Dr. Writht, George L., Jr., undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Dr. Zaloudek, Charles J., undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Dr. Zellis, Allan, undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Dr. Zimmerman, Hyman J., undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Dr. Zimmerman, Lorenz E., undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Photo of Dr. Al-Doory, Yousef, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photo of Dr. Alford, Crandall, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Photo of Dr. Blades, Brian, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Photo of Dr. Brennn, Gloria, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Photo of Dr. Brody, David, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Photo of Dr. Brown, Halla, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Photo of Dr. Coakley, Charls, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Photo of Dr. Cooper, Theodore, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Photo of Dr. Craft, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Photo of Dr. Devita, Vincent, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Photo of Dr. Dodek, Samuel, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Photo of Dr. Duncan, Harry, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Photo of Dr. Ecker, Henry, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Photo of Dr. Feffer, James, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Photo of Dr. Feffer, Henry Leon, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Photo of Dr. Fabro, Sergio, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Photo of Dr. Footer, Marvin, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Photo of Dr. Fox, Samuel, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Photo of Dr. Glew, Donald, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Photo of Dr. Hehrer, Gilbert, Ph.D., undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Photo of Dr. Hertz, Roy, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Photo of Dr. Hogness, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Photo of Dr. Iovine, Vincent, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Photo of Dr. Jacobson, Cecil, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Photo of Dr. Katz, Sol, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Photo of Dr. Kramer, Norman, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Photo of Krueger, Dean, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Photo of Dr. Klopp, Calvin, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Photo of Dr. Letterman, Gordon, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Photo of Dr. Levine, Sidney, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Photo of Dr. Lourie, Reginald, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Photo of Dr. Ludewig, Victor, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Photo of Dr. McKay, Douglas, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Photo of Dr. McKelway, William, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Photo of Dr. Maier, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Photo of Dr. Margileth, Andrew, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Photo of Dr. Marsh, William, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Photo of Dr. Miller, Frank, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Photo of Dr. Naughton, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Photo of Dr. Pierpont, Howard, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    News clippings relating to work of the doctors represented in Boxes 1 and 2
  - Photo of Dr. Romansky, Monroe, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Photo of Dr. Rosenbaum, Meyer, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Photo of Dr. Roudin, Gary, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Photo of Dr. Sank, Lawrence, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Photo of Dr. Schulman, Joseph, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Photo of Dr. Shumway, Norman, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Photo of Dr. Silver, Harold, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Photo of Dr. Smith, Benjamin, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Photo of Dr. Soyster, Peter, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Photo of Dr. Speck, George, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Photo of Dr. Stevens, Harold, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Photo of Dr. Stiller, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Photo of Dr. Treadwell, Carleton, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Photo of Dr. Thompson, Lewis, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Photo of Vita, Frank, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Photo of Dr. Webster, Thomas, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Photo of Dr. Weinstein, Jacob, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Photo of Dr. Weisburg, Paul, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Photo of Dr. Writht, George, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Photo of Dr. Zellis, Allan, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Photo of Dr. Zimmerman, Hyman, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Visual materials, 1983-1984; RG0045 Series 4; 0.5 Linear feet
  This series contains videotapes and a film. The material covers the dates 1983-84. These audio-visual materials are about the medical school.
  - "The Medical School" 3 1/2 inch reel, undated (Box 1, Reel 1)
    3 1/2 inch reel
  - GWU-Wyewitness News, WDVM TV General Report: GWU Intensive Unit. VHS Tape., 11/04/1983 (Box 1, Videocassette 2)
    Washington, DC: Friday Nov. 4 6:00 pm. General Report, GWU Intensive Unit. VHS tape
  - Medical School Commencement, VHS, 1984 (Box 1, Videocassette 3)
    VHS tape
  - GWU School of Medicine VHS, 1983 (Box 1, Videocassette 4)
    Videotaped by Congressional Color Photographers, copyright applied for. VHS tape
- Photographs, 1975-1983; RG0045 Series 5; 3 Linear feet